<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</title>
    <link>/academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:50:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Board Result</title>
      <link>/academics/board-result/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academics/board-result/</guid>
      <description> ICSE &amp;amp; ISC 2019 School Toppers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff &amp; Faculty</title>
      <link>/academics/staff-faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 06:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academics/staff-faculty/</guid>
      <description>A COMMITTED FACULTY AND STAFF Good teachers become great teachers by going beyond the call of duty and beyond the textbook. To do this, he or she must continue his/her education. There are conferences, workshops, and enduring education that could give our teachers that extra help in technology for their students. Madhusthali Vidyapeeth believes in the continuous up gradation of its teachers so that the students can gain maximum benefit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Occasion</title>
      <link>/academics/special-occasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 11:14:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academics/special-occasion/</guid>
      <description>The school will gives special importance to the celebration of the important days and annual days, to inculcate the feeling of nationalism, love for Alma Mater and gratitude to parents among the students. Special guidelines are set in advance and preparations start under the guidance of the teachers to celebrate these special days and rejuvenate the spirit and mind so that our culture is preserved and the students ensure the continuance of the cultural heritage of India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Activities</title>
      <link>/academics/school-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 18:57:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academics/school-activities/</guid>
      <description>In keeping with the theory of Multiple Intelligence, every child has some latent talent of which she/he should be made aware. At Madhusthali students are encouraged to express their joy in living through their talents and interests. Art &amp;amp; craft, Music and Sports routine is compulsory. For Activity Classes, the students choose from a host of activities like Music (Western and Indian), art, crafts, debates, quizzes, dramatics, elocution, creative writing, community service, web designing, gardening, tree planting and Marshal art etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>/academics/school-curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 17:33:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/academics/school-curriculum/</guid>
      <description>SCHOOL CURRICULUM Madhusthali Vidyapeeth follows the ICSE Curriculum which was earlier popularly called The Cambridge Board Exam. The Council for the Indian School Certificate Examinations administers the Indian Certificate of Secondary Education Examination (ICSE). The University of Cambridge Local Examinations Syndicate established the Council in 1958. The ICSE Examination has been designed to provide a course of general education in accordance with the recommendations of the New Education Policy 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>