<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</title>
    <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>71st Republic Day</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/71st-republic-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/71st-republic-day/</guid>
      <description>The 71st Republic Day was celebrated on January 26 at the Madhusthali Vidyapeeth stadium. The students took pride in glorifying and celebrating the spirit of unity and brotherhood. The event began with the hoisting of the Indian National Flag by the Honorable Chairman, Mr. Kishan Kumar Kejriwal along with the CEO Mr. Parthasarathi Chakraborthy, the Principal of MV, Mr. Bitan Biswas, the Principal of MITT, Mr. Deependra Nath, the Education Officer Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horse Riding</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/horse-riding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/horse-riding/</guid>
      <description>Horse Riding
Madhusthali Vidyapeeth has been consistent in keeping up to our commitments and being the only school in Deoghar Zone, we have introduced horse riding facilities for our students. Our main aim behind this endeavour is to uplift the status of this sport, up to the next level. We have the best horse riding coaches who train our students.
This horse riding experience is simply a few minute’s ride around the paddock, lead by our coaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scouts &amp; Guides Training Session &amp; Investiture Ceremony </title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/scouts-guides-training-session-investiture-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/scouts-guides-training-session-investiture-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>Scouts &amp;amp; Guides Training Session &amp;amp; Investiture Ceremony
Three days Scouts &amp;amp; Guides training session and Investiture Ceremony for the new aspirants started today from 9:30 am- 2:00 pm which was led by Mr.Dinesh Kumar Prasad- District Organizing Commissioner-Jamtara.
It was attended by all the new aspirants who had showed up in their complete uniform which was indeed a remarkable sight. Mr. Nilesh Kumar and Mr. Prasun Bagchi had initiated accordingly with the following session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEO Club Investiture Ceremony</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/leo-club-investiture-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/leo-club-investiture-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>LEO Club Investiture Ceremony
The Induction Ceremony is the symbolic beginning to a member’s service as a Lion. A thoughtful induction, followed by a thorough orientation and meaningful involvement in the club’s activities will keep a new member interested and engaged in the club. Keep in view the overall development of our students, Lions Club -322A conducted Investiture Ceremony for the newly 32 Madhusthalian Lion members 3rd October, 2018.
The ceremony was graced by Ln.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International School Award 2018-21</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-school-award-2018-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 10:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-school-award-2018-21/</guid>
      <description>The ISA project infused a thrill and excitement into the classroom teaching. The gamut of interdisciplinary activities shared with the teachers and the students of the partner schools added a global perspective not only to those activities but attitudes were transformed for life! ISA turned out to be a celebration of life and knowledge, a celebration which touched and transformed everyone, enriching the Teaching–Learning process.
The ISA has proved to be a journey of discovering ourselves, over reaching our capabilities and setting newer benchmarks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annual Day Celebrations</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/annual-day-celebrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/annual-day-celebrations/</guid>
      <description>Annual Day forms an integral part of our school activities. It is an occasion of celebration, felicitation, feast and festivity when students present not only their wonderful performances but also receive honours for their achievements in the ICSE &amp;amp; ISC Examinations, Academic excellences and other special categories.
The Annual Day Program, woven around the theme ‘Navrasa’ was successfully observed on 6th July, 2019 at the Multi-purpose hall. The school was decorated elegantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLESSING CEREMONY 2020</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/blessing-ceremony-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/blessing-ceremony-2020/</guid>
      <description>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth celebrated a good luck party for the incredible students of class X and XII who are going to appear in their forthcoming Board exams.The host for the event was Class XI. They had invited our honourable chairman, all the teachers and staffs of the school along with the Principal MV and the Administrator as special invitees to grace the occasion and boost up the morale of Class X and XII students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Visit</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/bank-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/bank-visit/</guid>
      <description>Altogether 11 (Eleven) Commerce students of classes X &amp;amp; XI were escorted by Mr. R.K Thakur (Commerce Department) to visit the HDFC bank, Madhupur Branch . It was their maiden visit to a bank where the Branch Manager Mr. Vivekanada Roy greeted everyone warmly.
Getting to grip with the idea of monetary value and the different denominations of bank notes is one of the financial lesson which we aimed at while taking our students for a visit to bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHILDREN&#39;S DAY CELEBRATION</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/children-s-day-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/children-s-day-celebration/</guid>
      <description>On 14th Nov, 2019 Madhusthali Family, celebrated Children&amp;rsquo;s Day in a grand manner commemorating 130th birthday of Pt. Jawaharlal Nehru. Teachers took the role of the students for theday as they conducted the special assembly with the saraswati vandana, the Shlokas, the Speech, the Day&amp;rsquo;s Thought and the News headlines. The morning section celebrated the day with great fun and the little talents performed various characters through Fancy dress. The teachers staged a variety of programmes in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COLOURING &amp; DRAWING COMPETITION </title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/colouring-drawing-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/colouring-drawing-competition/</guid>
      <description>A Drawing Competition was organized for Nursery to VIII. It was a day where we saw students’ creativity exploding in every piece of art. It was a wonderful opportunity to think out of the box. The competition not only served its sole purpose but also gave them a platform to display their vivid ideas and learn more by interacting with others in displaying the beautiful blending of colours. It also enhanced awareness amongst students as students were highly excited to show their creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Celebration</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/christmas-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/christmas-celebration/</guid>
      <description>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth, Celebrated Christmas day with great fervour and enthusiasm. The entire school vibrated with the echoes of Christmas Carol and Christmas medley by students of Class IV- VII.
The Pre-primary wing wore a festive look with bells, streamers and a beautiful decorated Christmas tree. The tiny tots of classes Nursery to II had performed a wonderful dance. The children were told about the birth of Lord Jesus and the legend of Santa Claus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clay Modelling Activity</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/clay-modelling-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/clay-modelling-activity/</guid>
      <description>Clay modelling is a great way to help children to develop imagination and spark creativity. Our school organized clay modelling activity for the class K.G. to II, Wherein the students participated enthusiastically. It enhanced their gross motor skills and creativity.
Through this activity students discovered how to make basic forms, develop hand – brain coordination, agility and fine motor skills. Practising the art of clay modelling gives children many opportunities to be creative and can also result in longer attention spans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dramatics &amp; Communication Skills Workshop</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/dramatics-communication-skills-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/dramatics-communication-skills-workshop/</guid>
      <description>A wonderful session on Dramatics was conducted as the students were seen in the best of their spirits.
Morning Session (Dramatics):
The Session was based on the introduction of theatre and its ethics. Students were shown videos and clippings of various forms of dramas on the topic “Intimate Space”.
It was indeed a wonderful and unique experience for them as they were given a task to answer as to why were they interested in taking part in Dramatics?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTER HOUSE HINDI DEBATE COMPETITION 2019</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-hindi-debate-competition-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-hindi-debate-competition-2019/</guid>
      <description>On 23rd Nov, 2019 Madhusthali Vidyapeeth organised a Hindi Debate Competition in the auditorium. Students participated in two categories.
 Junior Category - VI to VIII Senior Category - IX &amp;amp; XI  The moderator for the debate was Mr. Dwarika Prasad. Mrs. Shabnam Parveen and Mrs. Rubi Kumari were the Judges for the event. Mr. Samgeet Sundor Mondal was as the scorer. Eight students were selected from each house who were divided into two categories – FOR and AGAINST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL YOGA DAY</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-yoga-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-yoga-day-1/</guid>
      <description>INTERNATIONAL YOGA DAY
“Yoga is the journey of the self, through the self, to the self”
-Bhagavad Gita
To maintain a balance between oneself and environment is necessary for every human. Despite nowadays greater emotional as well as physical needs are given more priority. This is a reason why people suffer more stress, anxiety and also insomnia which is mainly due to improper lifestyle and physical exercise. Therefore, we need methods and techniques for the attainment of health and harmony; in this respect, yoga acts as an aid to one’s health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Visit</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/industrial-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/industrial-visit/</guid>
      <description>An Industrial visit has its own importance in the career of a student who will be pursuing a professional degree. It is considered to be a part of the school curriculum and the objectives of an industrial visit is to provide students with an insight regarding the internal working of an industry. We know, theoretical knowledge is not enough for making a good professional career. With an aim to go beyond academics, industrial visits are organized in our school to provide students a practical perspective on the world of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter House English Recitation Competition</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-english-recitation-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-english-recitation-competition/</guid>
      <description>“VERSES VS VERSES”
An Inter House English Recitation Competition &amp;lsquo;Verses vs Verses &amp;rsquo; which snatched everyone’s attention was based on the theme- FRIENDSHIP, PATRIOTISM and HOPE. It was anchored by Shivangi Singh of Class – V. This Competition was specially organized to enhance the confidence and speaking skills and develop appreciation in literature for the students.
The competition was adjudged by our respected teachers Mrs. Vinita Bose and Mr. Rupam Mukherjee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter House Hindi Recitation Competition</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-hindi-recitation-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/inter-house-hindi-recitation-competition/</guid>
      <description>The Inter House Hindi Recitation Competition &amp;lsquo;SURBHI &amp;rsquo; was held on 29th November, 2019 in MV campus. Class III, IV &amp;amp; V were involved in this competition. The theme of the competition were Std. III- Prarthana (Prayer) , Std.IV – Prakriti( Nature) &amp;amp; Std. V-Desh Bhakti (Patriotism). It was anchored by Aditi Rani of Std. IV.
The competition was Judged by Mrs. Lata Singh and Mrs. Rubi Kumari. Mr. Soumen Dutta was in charge as a scorer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Yoga Day Celebration on 21st June, 2020</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-yoga-day-celebration-on-21st-june-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/international-yoga-day-celebration-on-21st-june-2020/</guid>
      <description>The 6th International Yoga Day was celebrated on Sunday, 21st June, 2020 on the MCKV Zoom meeting with great enthusiasm and vigour under the guidance and co-operation of the Principal of Madhusthali Vidyapeeth, Mr. Bitan Biswas and Sports Coordinator, Mr. Nirmallya Ghosh. Almost 170 participants took part in that event. Chairman sir, CEO sir , HR madam, Education officer, Administrator and respective heads, faculty members, non teaching and adminstrative staff, and the family members of the staff of MCKV, MV, MIPS, MITT participated in the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JANMASTHAMI CELEBRATION</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/janmasthami-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/janmasthami-celebration/</guid>
      <description>The Morning Assembly was conducted by Vindhya House on 23rd August, 2019.
It started with a prayer by school choir.
Miss. Mahima Marandi of Class IX conducted the special assembly followed by some beautiful thoughts and news which was delivered by Master Adab of Class – X.
Thereon, Master Tausif Ansari of Class – X shared about the significance of the festival.
Special attraction of the assembly was Miss. EmaanTauquirand Master Shivansh Pandey of Nursery, who were dressed as Radha and Krishna that gathered everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAY DAY SPECIAL ASSEMBLY</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/may-day-special-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/may-day-special-assembly/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day, also known as ‘International Workers’ Day’, was celebrated in the school Special Assembly which was conducted by Master Arvind Kumar of Std. X who led the assembly into Gayatri Mantra, National Pledge &amp;amp; Speech, marking the day as significant one. The students were highlighted the historical events that contributed to the emergence of labor rights and the significance of the day in the present day. Gifts were handed over to all the Group D staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONLINE GURU PURNIMA CELEBRATION ON 5TH JULY, 2020</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-guru-purnima-celebration-on-5th-july-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-guru-purnima-celebration-on-5th-july-2020/</guid>
      <description>GURU PURNIMA CELEBRATION AT MADHUSTHALI VIDYAPEETH 2020
Guru Purnima is a tradition dedicated to all the spiritual and academic Gurus, who are evolved or enlightened humans, ready to share their wisdom with very little or no monetary expectation, based on Karma Yoga.
In keeping with the tradition of revering the gurus for their invaluable contribution in shaping the minds and characters of young people, the students of Madhusthali Vidyapeeth observed Guru Purnima for their beloved teachers on July 5, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Father’s Day Celebration </title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-father-s-day-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-father-s-day-celebration/</guid>
      <description>Father’s Day is a celebration, honoring fathers and celebrating fatherhood - an affectionate paternal bond and the influence of fathers in society.
Students from Class Nursery to XII of Madhusthali Vidyapeeth celebrated Father’s Day with a lot of enthusiasm in the Online due to pandemic fervor.
The event took off with beautiful songs, dance, lovely poetry dedicated by the children to their fathers. A photo booth with props was also set up for fathers and children to click photos, as pictures are a way to freeze those special memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Inter House Hindi Debate Competition 2020-21</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-inter-house-hindi-debate-competition-2020-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-inter-house-hindi-debate-competition-2020-21/</guid>
      <description>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth organized Inter House Hindi Debate Competition for Class VIII-X with the theme “Samvad” in the zoom meeting. The topic for classes VIII-X was ‘Prakriti Jansankhya Ko Niyantrit Karti Hai’.
Total 08 participants from four houses– Aravali, Nilgiri, Shivalik and Vindhya participated enthusiastically and spoke candidly for and against the given topic presented their views expressively. They cited reasons and supported them with suitable examples from real life, to justify their stand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Rath Yatra Festival Celebration in Madhusthali Vidyapeeth on 23rd June, 2020</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-rath-yatra-festival-celebration-in-madhusthali-vidyapeeth-on-23rd-june-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/online-rath-yatra-festival-celebration-in-madhusthali-vidyapeeth-on-23rd-june-2020/</guid>
      <description>Ratha Yatra is an ancient festival associated with Lord Jagannath, Lord Balabhadra and Lord Subhadra. The annual festival is celebrated every year on the second day in the bright fortnight of Ashadha month. During the festival, the Holy Trinity comes out of the sanctum sanctorum to visit their place of birth.
Madhusthali Vidyapeeth celebrated Rath Yatra festival on 23rd June, 2020. During this locked down period students were eager to show their activities to celebrate the festival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARENTS ORIENTATION PROGRAMME</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/parents-orientation-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/parents-orientation-programme/</guid>
      <description>PARENTS ORIENTATION PROGRAMME
“A parent is a teacher at home and a teacher is a parent in school and the child is the centre of our universe.”
Under the able guidance of our Respected Vice- Chairman and our Principal, an Orientation Programme was organized for the parents of new admissions of class XI at the multi-purpose hall on 25th June, 2019. The aim was to familiarize the parents, “as partners in progress” with the curriculum, rules and regulations of the school, teaching methodologies and the co-scholastic activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RAKHI MAKING COMPETITION</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/rakhi-making-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/rakhi-making-competition/</guid>
      <description>Rakhi making competition was conducted in which students participated with great zeal and enthusiasm. It was a class wise competition.
Along with house-hold materials, they also used different materials like– Biscuits, Cashew nuts, Rice, Cloves, Match sticks, Thread, Glitter paper and Ear buds too, which made their Rakhis quite different and special. Certificates were awarded to the winners. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rath Yatra Special Assembly</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/rath-yatra-special-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/rath-yatra-special-assembly/</guid>
      <description>On the auspicious day of Rath Yatra special assembly was conducted by the students of Aravali house on 4th July,2019 in Madhusthali Vidyapeeth. The chariot was decorated and a banner on Rath Yatra was prepared by students of class VIII, IX and X.
The assembly started with Gyatri Mantra followed by National Pledge and then a short speech was delivered by Faria Hamid, student of class XI focusing on grand celebration of Rath Yatra festival in Odisha .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SARASWATI PUJA CELEBRATION - 2020</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/saraswati-puja-celebration-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/saraswati-puja-celebration-2020/</guid>
      <description>Saraswati puja was celebrated with great fervour on 30th January , 2020 at Madhusthali Vidyapeeth . The Temple was well decorated with garlands. All the teachers and students gathered at the school temple in the morning to celebrate the day. Puja was offered by the students of Class X along with other students. MITT and MIPS students, teachers and staffs also joined in this auspicious occasion. It was an attempt to preserve the Indian culture, to impart a sense of respect towards long established traditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Introduction</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/self-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/self-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Self instruction activity was conducted in the Pre Primary section. All the students from classes Nursery-II actively participated in the activity. The objective of this activity was to help even the shyest students to open up a bit and try out to express themselves and communicate in English and develop language skills in the classroom.
Students took an opportunity to come forward and introduce themselves and speak about their families in front of everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THUMB PRINTING ACTIVITY</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/thumb-printing-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/thumb-printing-activity/</guid>
      <description>‘Thumb Printing Activity’ was conducted in pre- primary section to boost our students’ artistic skill. This activity helped students to build hand-eye coordination, muscle control and dexterity. Moreover, it allows the young child to work with the medium, moving it around, blending it and creating anything from an abstract expression to explore their own creativity. It was based on various topics like Bunch of flowers, Vegetable, Insects, Electronic gadgets, Scenery etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teachers Day Celebration</title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/teachers-day-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/teachers-day-celebration/</guid>
      <description>Students solemnly celebrated Teacher’s Day with great gusto and gaiety. The program was led with a prayer song by the school choir, followed by an innovative inauguration followed by lighting of the lamp in remembrance of Dr. Sarvepalli Radhakrishnan.
The cultural program began with a Bharatnatyam dance performance by Miss Sreeja Sur of Std. XII. Students performed a scintillating display expressing their ardent love and recognition of the hard work put in by the teachers towards their development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop on Life Skills </title>
      <link>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/workshop-on-life-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://madhusthali.edu.in/news/workshop-on-life-skills/</guid>
      <description>“In a constantly changing environment, having life skills is an essential part of being able to meet the challenges of everyday life.
Life skills provide children with important tools for development, such as independent thinking, how to socialize and make new friends and how to take action in situations where their parents or teachers may not be around to help or intervene (eg. dealing with a bully or personal insecurities and fears).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>