<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</title>
    <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:50:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Board Result</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/board-result/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/board-result/</guid>
      <description> ICSE 2017 School Toppers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Captain</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:07:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-captain/</guid>
      <description>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth has forever been an institution of creativity and innovation. The motto of the school has always been to craft students into successful global citizens of the future. The school curriculum goes beyond academics and inculcates the desire to excel in fields like sports and music along with academics, amongst the students. I welcome everyone to join our family and be a part of the amazing experience amidst nature at Madhusthali Vidyapeeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Event</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/events/test-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 08:43:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/events/test-event/</guid>
      <description>Aliquet porttitor lacus, luctus accumsan tortor posuere ac ut consequat semper viverra nam libero justo? Ut enim blandit volutpat maecenas volutpat blandit aliquam etiam erat velit, scelerisque in dictum non, consectetur a erat nam at lectus urna duis convallis convallis tellus, id interdum velit laoreet. Blandit cursus risus, at ultrices? Ac odio tempor orci dapibus ultrices in iaculis nunc sed augue lacus, viverra vitae congue eu, consequat ac felis donec?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Founders Day</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/events/founders-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 19:21:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/events/founders-day/</guid>
      <description>Amet cursus sit amet, dictum sit amet justo donec enim diam, vulputate ut pharetra sit amet, aliquam id diam maecenas.
Sed vulputate odio ut enim blandit volutpat maecenas volutpat blandit aliquam etiam erat velit, scelerisque in dictum non, consectetur! Mauris pellentesque pulvinar pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is a Long Headline With Short News Text</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/this-is-a-long-headline-with-short-news-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 14:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/this-is-a-long-headline-with-short-news-text/</guid>
      <description>Euismod nisi porta lorem mollis aliquam ut porttitor leo a diam sollicitudin tempor id eu nisl nunc mi ipsum, faucibus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/news-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 14:44:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/news-2/</guid>
      <description>Euismod nisi porta lorem mollis aliquam ut porttitor leo a diam sollicitudin tempor id eu nisl nunc mi ipsum, faucibus!
Et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas integer eget aliquet nibh praesent tristique magna sit amet purus gravida quis blandit turpis cursus in hac habitasse platea dictumst. Urna neque viverra justo, nec ultrices dui sapien eget mi proin sed libero enim, sed faucibus turpis in eu mi bibendum neque!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News 1</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/news-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 14:43:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/news/news-1/</guid>
      <description>Euismod nisi porta lorem mollis aliquam ut porttitor leo a diam sollicitudin tempor id eu nisl nunc mi ipsum, faucibus! Et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas integer eget aliquet nibh praesent tristique magna sit amet purus gravida quis blandit turpis cursus in hac habitasse platea dictumst. Urna neque viverra justo, nec ultrices dui sapien eget mi proin sed libero enim, sed faucibus turpis in eu mi bibendum neque! Ultricies leo integer malesuada nunc vel risus commodo viverra maecenas accumsan, lacus vel facilisis volutpat, est velit egestas dui, id.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notice for Staff</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/notice/notice-for-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 12:44:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/notice/notice-for-staff/</guid>
      <description>Et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas integer eget aliquet nibh praesent tristique magna sit amet purus gravida quis blandit turpis cursus in hac habitasse platea. At imperdiet dui accumsan sit amet nulla facilisi morbi tempus iaculis urna, id? Nisl tincidunt eget nullam non nisi est, sit amet facilisis magna etiam tempor, orci eu lobortis elementum, nibh tellus molestie nunc, non blandit massa. Diam quam nulla porttitor massa id.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notice for Class X</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/notice/notice-for-class-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 12:43:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/notice/notice-for-class-x/</guid>
      <description>Et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas integer eget aliquet nibh praesent tristique magna sit amet purus gravida quis blandit turpis cursus in hac habitasse platea. At imperdiet dui accumsan sit amet nulla facilisi morbi tempus iaculis urna, id? Nisl tincidunt eget nullam non nisi est, sit amet facilisis magna etiam tempor, orci eu lobortis elementum, nibh tellus molestie nunc, non blandit massa. Diam quam nulla porttitor massa id.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Gallery with Forestry</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/gallery/test-gallary-with-forestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 07:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/gallery/test-gallary-with-forestry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/gallery/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:43:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/gallery/screenshots/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Life</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/lifestyle/daily-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 13:49:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/lifestyle/daily-life/</guid>
      <description>BOARDING HOUSE SCHEDULE SUMMER (MONDAY TO FRIDAY) 05:00am Rouse Bell 05:15am to  06:00am Morning Exercise 06:00am to  07:00am Bath &amp;amp; Change  07:00am to  01:20pm School Schedule  07:55am to  08:25amBreak Fast  01:20pm to  01:50pm Lunch  01:50pm to  02:30pm Rest Time  02:30pm to  04:15pm Self Study  04:15pm to  05:15pm Games  05:15pm to  05:45pm Wash &amp;amp; Change  05:45pm to  06:15pm Snacks  06:15pm to  08:00pm Study Time  08:00pm to  08:30pm Dinner  08:30pm to  09:30pmT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life @ Madhusthali</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/lifestyle/life-madhusthali/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 13:38:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/lifestyle/life-madhusthali/</guid>
      <description>CULTURE Madhusthali makes sure that the students get enriched with Indian culture. For this we have weekly hobby classes. These classes are specially allotted for the students, are crafted in a manner that the students get informed about Indian as well as western forms of art and culture. From painting to literature to cultural values, students are taught everything from India as well as the world over. This helps them to increase their knowledge about the world and the country they live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff &amp; Faculty</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/staff-faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 11:38:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/staff-faculty/</guid>
      <description>A COMMITTED FACULTY AND STAFF Good teachers become great teachers by going beyond the call of duty and beyond the textbook. To do this, he or she must continue his/her education. There are conferences, workshops, and enduring education that could give our teachers that extra help in technology for their students. Madhusthali Vidyapeeth believes in the continuous up gradation of its teachers so that the students can gain maximum benefit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Occasion</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/special-occasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 11:14:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/special-occasion/</guid>
      <description>The school will gives special importance to the celebration of the important days and annual days, to inculcate the feeling of nationalism, love for Alma Mater and gratitude to parents among the students. Special guidelines are set in advance and preparations start under the guidance of the teachers to celebrate these special days and rejuvenate the spirit and mind so that our culture is preserved and the students ensure the continuance of the cultural heritage of India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Activities</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/school-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 18:57:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/school-activities/</guid>
      <description>In keeping with the theory of Multiple Intelligence, every child has some latent talent of which she/he should be made aware. At Madhusthali students are encouraged to express their joy in living through their talents and interests. Art &amp;amp; craft, Music and Sports routine is compulsory. For Activity Classes, the students choose from a host of activities like Music (Western and Indian), art, crafts, debates, quizzes, dramatics, elocution, creative writing, community service, web designing, gardening, tree planting and Marshal art etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/school-curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 17:33:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/academics/school-curriculum/</guid>
      <description>SCHOOL CURRICULUM Madhusthali Vidyapeeth follows the ICSE Curriculum which was earlier popularly called The Cambridge Board Exam. The Council for the Indian School Certificate Examinations administers the Indian Certificate of Secondary Education Examination (ICSE). The University of Cambridge Local Examinations Syndicate established the Council in 1958. The ICSE Examination has been designed to provide a course of general education in accordance with the recommendations of the New Education Policy 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Mission</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/our-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 16:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/our-mission/</guid>
      <description>Aap Deepo Bhava (Be your own light) –Indicates inner strength and courage. The aim of the school is to prepare the students academically, physically, psychologically, spiritually and morally for entering any walk of life by seeking to develop character, promote esprit-de-corps and desire to serve the country in any capacity with efficiency, industry and zeal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Vision</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/our-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 16:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/our-vision/</guid>
      <description>Our vision encompasses the achievement of an all-round development of the child into a young man or woman possessing an optimum of those values which will make him or her a better human being and a constructive citizen of the country, keeping in view the following objectives :
 To prepare the students to live their lives fully and successfully by imparting them the vision of life To instill in the students the spirit of service in all walks of life so that they become responsible citizens of the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Prayers</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:04:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-prayers/</guid>
      <description>Daily Morning Prayer O, Father give me prosperity, health and wisdom, without measure, not from earthly sources, but from your all possessing, all powerful and all bountiful hands. Help me to think the right thing, to speak the right thing and to do the right thing. Keep me free from anger, hatred, greed and all other vices. Bless my parents, my brothers and sisters, my friends and foes and all those around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timing and Visiting Hours</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/timing-visiting_hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:04:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/timing-visiting_hours/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE NOTE THE TIME AND DAY FOR MAKING CALL TO YOUR WARD    HOSTEL TELEPHONE NO&amp;rsquo;S. MONDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. TUESDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. WEDNESDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. THURSDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. FRIDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. SATURDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM.     Junior Boys &amp;amp; All Girls 8092586239 I, II, IV V, VI, VIII IX, XI VII, VIII I, II, IV, XI V, VI, VII, IX   Senior Boys 9234106469, 9234179662 VI,VII VIII, IX X, XI, XII VI, VII VIII, XI IX, X, XII    VISITING HOURS:  Parents and local guardians may visit their wards only on weekends of the month and public holidays between 9:00 am and 04:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees Structure</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/fees-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:06:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/fees-structure/</guid>
      <description>FEES-STRUCTURE : 2017-18  Particulars Class I to II Class III to VII Class VIII to X Class XI &amp; XII   Cost of Prospectus &amp; Registration Form Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00   Admission Fee (paid at the time of admission only. Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00   Security Deposit (Refundable) Paid at the time of Admission Rs. 15,000.00 Rs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules and Regulations</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/rules-regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:06:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/rules-regulations/</guid>
      <description>A high standard of behaviour is maintained and children are taught to give due respect to their elders and to appreciate and regard the opinions of others. Thus discipline plays a vital role in our institution. What follows is a set of instructions and guide lines for the student community as well as for their parents
General Rules  Guardians are requested not to celebrate their ward&amp;rsquo;s birth anniversaries in the school campus as all guardians are not financially well off to spend large sums of money on this occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Uniform</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:06:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/school-uniform/</guid>
      <description>SCHOOL UNIFORM FOR BOYS (IN SUMMER): NURSERY TO II : White on blue line Shirt, Blue Half Pant, School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.
CLASSES III TO IV : White on blue line Shirt, Blue Half Pant, House T-Shirt School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.
CLASSES V TO XII : White on blue line Shirt, Blue full Pant, House T-Shirt School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chairman&#39;s Message</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/chairmans-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 15:37:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/chairmans-message/</guid>
      <description>Starting the struggle of life at a very early stage, I have traversed the tough road to success through myriad experiences and experiments. In the quest for success, I ventured into many enterprises, some of which met with huge success while others were moderate. Through these enterprises, I have come across thousands of people, a few successful and still rising on the path of success, and others merely dragging on with their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message from the Principal</title>
      <link>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/principals-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 15:37:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://139.59.37.116/madhusthali/about/principals-message/</guid>
      <description>Starting the struggle of life at a very early stage, I have traversed the tough road to success through myriad experiences and experiments. In the quest for success, I ventured into many enterprises, some of which met with huge success while others were moderate. Through these enterprises, I have come across thousands of people, a few successful and still rising on the path of success, and others merely dragging on with their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>