<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Madhusthali Vidyapeeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 09:27:47 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees Structure</title>
      <link>/about/fees-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/fees-structure/</guid>
      <description>FEES-STRUCTURE : 2020-2021
 Particulars Class I to II Class III to VII Class VIII to X Class XI &amp; XII   Cost of Prospectus &amp; Registration Form Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00 Rs. 750.00   Admission Fee (paid at the time of admission only. Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.00   Security Deposit (Refundable) Paid at the time of Admission Rs. 15,000.00 Rs. 15,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vice Chairman Message</title>
      <link>/about/managing-trustee-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 08:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/managing-trustee-message/</guid>
      <description>With immense pride and great pleasure I welcome you at the Madhusthali Vidyapeeth. You could be a parent, a student, a staff member or anyone interested in gaining deeper insights into the functioning and learning environment of our exciting world.
I invite you to visit our stunning campus to help you understand coherently, why our school provides the best environment for your little-ones and young-adults. Right from its inception to now, our institution has marched forward to spread the light of education and pave the path of academic excellence for every student.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Captain</title>
      <link>/about/school-captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 14:07:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/school-captain/</guid>
      <description>Madhusthali Vidyapeeth has forever been an institution of creativity and innovation. The motto of the school has always been to craft students into successful global citizens of the future. The school curriculum goes beyond academics and inculcates the desire to excel in fields like sports and music along with academics, amongst the students. I welcome everyone to join our family and be a part of the amazing experience amidst nature at Madhusthali Vidyapeeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Mission</title>
      <link>/about/our-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 16:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/our-mission/</guid>
      <description>Aap Deepo Bhava (Be your own light) –Indicates inner strength and courage. The aim of the school is to prepare the students academically, physically, psychologically, spiritually and morally for entering any walk of life by seeking to develop character, promote esprit-de-corps and desire to serve the country in any capacity with efficiency, industry and zeal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Vision</title>
      <link>/about/our-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 16:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/our-vision/</guid>
      <description>Our vision encompasses the achievement of an all-round development of the child into a young man or woman possessing an optimum of those values which will make him or her a better human being and a constructive citizen of the country, keeping in view the following objectives :
 To prepare the students to live their lives fully and successfully by imparting them the vision of life To instill in the students the spirit of service in all walks of life so that they become responsible citizens of the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Prayers</title>
      <link>/about/school-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:04:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/school-prayers/</guid>
      <description>Daily Morning Prayer O, Father give me prosperity, health and wisdom, without measure, not from earthly sources, but from your all possessing, all powerful and all bountiful hands. Help me to think the right thing, to speak the right thing and to do the right thing. Keep me free from anger, hatred, greed and all other vices. Bless my parents, my brothers and sisters, my friends and foes and all those around me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timing and Visiting Hours</title>
      <link>/about/timing-visiting_hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:04:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/timing-visiting_hours/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE NOTE THE TIME AND DAY FOR MAKING CALL TO YOUR WARD    HOSTEL TELEPHONE NO&amp;rsquo;S. MONDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. TUESDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. WEDNESDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. THURSDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. FRIDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM. SATURDAY 08:30 PM. TO 09:30 PM.     Junior Boys &amp;amp; All Girls 8092586239 I, II, IV V, VI, VIII IX, XI VII, VIII I, II, IV, XI V, VI, VII, IX   Senior Boys 9234106469, 9234179662 VI,VII VIII, IX X, XI, XII VI, VII VIII, XI IX, X, XII    VISITING HOURS:  Parents and local guardians may visit their wards only on weekends of the month and public holidays between 9:00 am and 04:00 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules and Regulations</title>
      <link>/about/rules-regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:06:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/rules-regulations/</guid>
      <description>A high standard of behaviour is maintained and children are taught to give due respect to their elders and to appreciate and regard the opinions of others. Thus discipline plays a vital role in our institution. What follows is a set of instructions and guide lines for the student community as well as for their parents
General Rules  Guardians are requested not to celebrate their ward&amp;rsquo;s birth anniversaries in the school campus as all guardians are not financially well off to spend large sums of money on this occasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Uniform</title>
      <link>/about/school-uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:06:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/school-uniform/</guid>
      <description>SCHOOL UNIFORM FOR BOYS (IN SUMMER): NURSERY TO II : White on blue line Shirt, Blue Half Pant, School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.
CLASSES III TO IV : White on blue line Shirt, Blue Half Pant, House T-Shirt School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.
CLASSES V TO XII : White on blue line Shirt, Blue full Pant, House T-Shirt School tie, school belt, black shoes &amp;amp; white socks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message from the Principal</title>
      <link>/about/principals-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/principals-message/</guid>
      <description>Education is the making of a man. It is an enlightenment which is the sign of a civilized society. Culture comes from it and this grooms and shapes individuals and regulates their behaviour and attitude. The right attitude is needed to reach the right altitude of life.
We, at Madhusthali, endeavour to attain this. We pluck the children young and with our pupil centric atmosphere, we apply student friendly techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our inspiration …forever</title>
      <link>/about/chairmans-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/chairmans-message/</guid>
      <description>Shri Shyam Sunder Kejriwal, a prominent entrepreneur and philanthropist, strongly felt that the development of India as a modern, progressive, prosperous, and self-reliant country depended entirely on the creation of a well-informed and educated citizenry. It was with this vision that he established M. C. Kejriwal Vidyapeeth on 15 June 1997, and created, with a missionary zeal, an institution that would, one day, under his Chairmanship, be ranked among the top ten boys’ schools in the Kolkata region (Education World Survey, 2019).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>